Nitay Yacobovitch

054-6692505



https://nitayya.github.io/Nitay/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nitayya/



nitayya@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Expanding my skills by participating in a "Data Engineer" Certification course in Naya College 2 years experience as a BI Analyst for a product software company delivering ML and AI solution for US retailers and FCMG. Working with very large data sets using big data technologies (SQL, Python, Visualization Tools, ETL and more...)

Information Systems Management (Ben-Gurion University) Graduate

SKILLS

Development skills -

- Python Developed 'System output validator' tool that reduces the manual work of my team on it. The tool was
 developed using various libraries such as Pandas, NumPy, logging, sqlalchemy
- Java, OOP
- JS, PHP, HTML, CSS

Data Technologies-

- SQL proficiency
- Hadoop Framework, Kafka, NoSQL DBs, AWS infrastructure
- Cloud infrastructure (mainly AWS)
- DWH (including data modeling, ETL/ELT processes
- Visualization/BI tools: Tableau, Power-BI, Talend

CAREER

2020 - PRESENT

BI ANALYST

Sagarmatha

- Working with a US based retailer, to target personalized coupons within their loyalty program, including:
 - Querying from various large & complex data sets (SQL Server, Exasol), executing ad-hoc anylysis to detect patterns based on shopper's behavior to improve business decision making
 - Setup, calibrate, execute and monitor the personalization ML engine (Sagarmatha's propriety software)
 - Worked closely within a team of Data analysts and BI developers to define ETL processes and analytic reports
 - Responsibility for all on-going operation activities, while working with oversea customers and customer success team

2018 - 2020

ADMINISTRATIVE ROLE

"Atomchip Group" in BGU's Physics department

- Management of the team's purchases and budget
- Management of contact with different role-players in BGU (in charge of purchases, budget, research & administration)
- for team members traveling abroad and their international guests
- General logistical management of team's activity

EDUCATION

2017 - 2020

BEN-GURION UNIVERSITY

Information Systems Management

- Final project at University's Internal audit office with Sharepoint
- Main courses: OOP, BI, WEB, CRM, Databases, IT Infrastructure Algorithms and Complexity

2015

WINGATE INSTITUTE

Basketball Coaches Course